AFSCME, District Council 37 Photographs PHOTOS.247
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Many of these negatives depict major events in the Council's history, but appear to be copy negatives produced at a later date. This subseries also contains 113 negatives for the 1963 Fall Conference. Arrangement mirrors that of subseries in Series III: DC 37 History.
Subseries VII: I: DC 37 Subject Files Negatives, [1963]-[1975].
The bulk of these negatives are in 35mm format. They are arranged alphabetically by subject, with most of the images documenting the Council's Nurses' Aides Upgrading Program.
Subseries VII: J: DC 37 Subject Files 4x5 Negatives, [1957]-[1975].
Four negatives, arranged alphabetically by subject.
Subseries VII: K: General Subject Files Negatives, Undated.
One file of 35mm negatives from the "Cemetery" general subject file.
Subseries VII: L: Oversize Negatives, [1968]-[1989].
Sixteen files of oversize negatives; arrangement mirrors that of Series I-III. Some are copy negatives of 8x10 black and white prints.
Subseries VII: M: Miscellaneous, Undated.
This subseries contains a small number of 35 mm negatives that were loose or unidentified.
Series VIII: Slides, [1963]-1989.
This series contains images that mainly relate to the DC 37 History and Subject Files photographic prints series. Events documented include demonstrations, strikes, and a 1987 bargaining session between Council and New York City representatives. Many slides show DC 37 members on the job in various fields. Those depicting city agencies and departments may have come from the Council's Quality of Work Life (QWL) Committees. This series also contains commercial slides of New York City, Albany, and Washington, DC scenes, as well as images of various fires supplied by the New York City Fire Department.
NOTE: This collection is housed offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Arrangement
Organized into 8 series: I. Public Employee Press files; II. Locals files; III. DC 37 History; IV. DC 37 Subject files; V. General subject files; VI. Contact sheets; VII. Negatives; VIII. Slides
Series
I. Public Employee Press files
II. Locals files
III. DC 37 History
IV. DC 37 Subject files
V. General Subject files
VI. Contact Sheets
VII. Negatives
VIII. Slides
This collection is organized into 8 series:
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Separated from American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records (WAG 265) by Tamiment staff. The records of AFSCME, District Council 37 were donated by Lillian Roberts (executive director) on behalf of the AFSCME, District Council 37, in 2007. The accession numbers associated with this collection are 2007.012 and NPA.2003.065
Photographic prints.; Color slides.; Negatives (photographic); Contact sheets.; New York (N.Y.) |x Officials and employees |v Portraits.; Public employees.; Black-and-white photographs.; Municipal officials and employees |x Labor unions |z New York (State) |z New York.; Government employee unions |z New York (State) |z New York.; AFSCME; Gotbaum, Victor; Wurf, Jerry, 1919-; Taibi, Calogero; Hill, Stanley, 1936-; AFSCME. District Council 37 (New York, N.Y.) -- |v Periodicals; Roberts, Lillian; AFSCME. District Council 37 (New York, N.Y.); Roberts, Lillian
- Series I: Public Employee Press Files, [1959]-[2001].
  - Vol. 1 No. 1 Issue Date: Jun 12, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 1 No. 2 Issue Date: Jun 26, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 1 No. 5 Issue Date: Aug 7, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 1 No. 9 Issue Date: Oct 2, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 1 No. 10 Issue Date: Oct 16, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 1 No. 11 Issue Date: Oct 30, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 1 No. 13 Issue Date: Nov 27, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 2 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 5, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 2 No. 4 Issue Date: Feb 19, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 2 No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 4, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 2 No. 8 Issue Date: Apr 15, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 2 No. 9 Issue Date: Apr 29, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 2 No. 13 Issue Date: Jun 24, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 2 No. 17 Issue Date: Aug 19, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 2 No. 19 Issue Date: Sep 16, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 2 No. 20 Issue Date: Sep 30, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 4 No. 20 Issue Date: Sep 28, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 4 No. 24 Issue Date: Nov 23, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 4 No. 25 Issue Date: Dec 7, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 5 No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 1, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 5 No. 8 Issue Date: Apr 12, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Vol. 5 No. 9 Issue Date: Apr 26, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Vol. 5 No. 10 Issue Date: May 10, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Vol. 5 No. 11 Issue Date: May 24, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Vol. 5 No. 12 Issue Date: Jun 7, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Vol. 5 No. 13 Issue Date: Jun 21, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Vol. 5 No. 14 Issue Date: Jul 5, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Vol. 5 No. 15 Issue Date: Jul 19, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Vol. 5 No. 16 Issue Date: Aug 2, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Vol. 5 No. 19 Issue Date: Sep 13, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Vol. 5 No. 20 Issue Date: Sep 27, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Vol. 5 No. 21 Issue Date: Oct 11, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Vol. 5 No. 23 Issue Date: Nov 8, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Vol. 5 No. 24 Issue Date: Nov 22, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Vol. 5 No. 26 Issue Date: Dec 20, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Vol. 6 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 3, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Vol. 6 No. 3 Issue Date: Jan 31, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Vol. 6 No. 4 Issue Date: Feb 14, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Vol. 6 No. 12 Issue Date: Apr 10, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Vol. 6 No. 13 Issue Date: Apr 17, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Vol. 6 No. 14 Issue Date: Apr 24, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Vol. 6 No. 21 Issue Date: Jun 12, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Vol. 6 No. 22 Issue Date: Jun 19, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Vol. 6 No. 24 Issue Date: Jul 17, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Vol. 6 No. 27 Issue Date: Aug 28, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Vol. 6 No. 28 Issue Date: Sep 11, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Vol. 6 No. 29 Issue Date: Sep 25, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Vol. 6 No. 30 Issue Date: Oct 9, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Vol. 6 No. 32 Issue Date: Nov 6, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Vol. 7 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 1, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Vol. 7 No. 8 Issue Date: Apr 9, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Vol. 7 No. 9 Issue Date: Apr 23, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Vol. 7 No. 10 Issue Date: May 7, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Vol. 7 No. 11 Issue Date: May 21, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Vol. 7 No. 12 Issue Date: Jun 4, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Vol. 7 No. 13 Issue Date: Jun 18, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Vol. 7 No. 14 Issue Date: Jul 1965 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Vol. 7 No. 15 Issue Date: Aug 1965 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Vol. 7 No. 17 Issue Date: Oct 1, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Vol. 7 No. 19 Issue Date: Oct 29, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Vol. 7 No. 20 Issue Date: Nov 12, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Vol. 7 No. 22 Issue Date: Dec 10, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Vol. [8] No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 4, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Vol. [8] No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 4, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Vol. [8] No. 6 Issue Date: Mar 18, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Vol. 7 No. 7 Issue Date: Apr 1, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Vol. 7 No. 9 Issue Date: Apr 29, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Vol. 7 No. 11 Issue Date: May 27, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Vol. 7 No. 12 Issue Date: Jun 1966 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Vol. 7 No. 13 Issue Date: Jul 1966 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Vol. 7 No. 14 Issue Date: Aug 1966 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Vol. 7 No. 15 Issue Date: Sep 1966 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Vol. 7 No. 18 Issue Date: Nov 23, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Vol. 8 No. 3 Issue Date: Mar 8, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Vol. 8 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 29, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Vol. 8 No. 5 Issue Date: Apr 19, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Vol. 8 No. 6 Issue Date: May 10, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Vol. 8 No. 7 Issue Date: May 31, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Vol. 8 No. 8 Issue Date: Jun 21, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Vol. 8 No. 9 Issue Date: Jul 12, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Vol. 8 No. 10 Issue Date: Aug 23, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Vol. 8 No. 11 Issue Date: Sep 13, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Vol. 8 No. 12 Issue Date: Oct 4, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Vol. 8 No. 13 Issue Date: Oct 25, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Vol. 8 No. 14 Issue Date: Nov 15, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Vol. 8 No. 15 Issue Date: Dec 6, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Vol. 8 No. [16] Issue Date: Dec 27, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Vol. 9 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 24, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Vol. 9 No. 2 Issue Date: Feb 28, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Vol. 9 No. 3 Issue Date: Mar 20, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Vol. 9 No. 4 Issue Date: Apr 17, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Vol. 9 No. 5 Issue Date: May 8, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Vol. 9 No. 6 Issue Date: May 29, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Vol. 9 No. 7 Issue Date: Jun 26, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Vol. 9 No. 8 Issue Date: Jul 24, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Vol. 9 No. 9 Issue Date: Sep 4, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Vol. 9 No. 10 Issue Date: Sep 25, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Vol. 9 No. 11 Issue Date: Oct 16, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Vol. 9 No. 12 Issue Date: Nov 6, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Vol. 9 No. 13 Issue Date: Nov 27, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Vol. 9 No. 14 Issue Date: Dec 18, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Vol. 10 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 17, 1969, [Dec 17, 1969] (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Vol. 10 No. 2 Issue Date: Feb 7, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Vol. 10 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 28, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 10 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 21, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 10 No. 5 Issue Date: Apr 11, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 10 No. 6 Issue Date: May 2, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 10 No. 7 Issue Date: May 23, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 10 No. 8 Issue Date: Jun 13, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 10 No. 9 Issue Date: Jul 11, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 10 No. 10 Issue Date: Aug 29, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 10 No. 11 Issue Date: Sep 19, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 10 No. 12 Issue Date: Oct 10, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 10 No. 13 Issue Date: Oct 31, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 10 No. 14 Issue Date: Nov 21, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 10 No. 15 Issue Date: Dec 12, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 11 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 2, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 11 No. 2 Issue Date: Jan 30, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 11 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 20, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 11 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 20, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 11 No. 5 Issue Date: Apr 17, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 11 No. 6 Issue Date: May 8, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 11 No. 7 Issue Date: May 29, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 11 No. 8 Issue Date: Jun 19, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Vol. 11 No. 9 Issue Date: Jul 10, 1970 (I) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Vol. 11 No. 9 Issue Date: Jul 10, 1970 (II) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Vol. 11 No. 10 Issue Date: Aug 28, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 11 No. 11 Issue Date: Sep 18, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 11 No. 12 Issue Date: Oct 9, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 11 No. 13 Issue Date: Oct 30, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 11 No. 14 Issue Date: Nov 20, 1970 (I) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 11 No. 14 Issue Date: Nov 20, 1970 (II) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 11 No. 15 Issue Date: Dec 11, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 12 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 1, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 12 No. 2 Issue Date: Jan 29, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 12 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 19, 1971 (I) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 12 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 19, 1971 (II) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 12 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 12, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 12 No. 5 Issue Date: Apr 2, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 12 No. 6 Issue Date: Apr 23, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 12 No. 7 Issue Date: May 14, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 12 No. 8 Issue Date: Jun 18, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 12 No. 9 Issue Date: Jul 2, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 12 No. 10 Issue Date: Jul 16, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 12 No. 11 Issue Date: Aug 27, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 12 No. 12 Issue Date: Sep 17, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 12 No. 13 Issue Date: Oct 8, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 12 No. 14 Issue Date: Oct 29, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 12 No. 15 Issue Date: Nov 19, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 12 No. 16 Issue Date: Dec 10, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 12 No. 17 Issue Date: Dec 31, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 13 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 28, 1972 (I) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 13 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 28, 1972 (II) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 13 No. 2 Issue Date: Feb 11, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 13 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 25, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 13 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 10, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 13 No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 24, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 13 No. 6 Issue Date: Apr 7, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 13 No. 7 Issue Date: Apr 21, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 13 No. 8 Issue Date: May 5, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 13 No. 9 Issue Date: May 19, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 13 No. 10 Issue Date: Jun 2, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 13 No. 11 Issue Date: Jun 16, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 13 No. 12 Issue Date: Jul 7, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 13 No. 13 Issue Date: Jul 21, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 13 No. 14 Issue Date: Aug 31, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 13 No. 15 Issue Date: Sep 15, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Vol. 13 No. 16 Issue Date: Sep 29, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Vol. 13 No. 17 Issue Date: Oct 13, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Vol. 13 No. 18 Issue Date: Oct 27, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Vol. 13 No. 19 Issue Date: Nov 10, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Vol. 13 No. 20 Issue Date: Nov 24, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Vol. 13 No. 21 Issue Date: Dec 8, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Vol. 13 No. 22 Issue Date: Dec 22, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Vol. 14 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 19, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Vol. 14 No. 2 Issue Date: Feb 2, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 14 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 16, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 14 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 2, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 14 No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 16, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 14 No. 6 Issue Date: Apr 1, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 14 No. 7 Issue Date: Apr 13, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 14 No. 8 Issue Date: Apr 27, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 14 No. 9 Issue Date: May 11, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 14 No. 10 Issue Date: Jun 1, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 14 No. 11 Issue Date: Jun 15, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 14 No. 12 Issue Date: Jun 29, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 14 No. 13 Issue Date: Jul 13, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 14 No. 14 Issue Date: Aug 24, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 14 No. 15 Issue Date: Sep 7, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 14 No. 16 Issue Date: Sep 21, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 14 No. 17 Issue Date: Oct 5, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 14 No. 18 Issue Date: Oct 19, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 14 No. 19 Issue Date: Nov 2, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 14 No. 20 Issue Date: Nov 16, 1973 (I) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 14 No. 20 Issue Date: Nov 16, 1973 (II) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 14 No. 21 Issue Date: Nov 30, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Vol. 14 No. 22 Issue Date: Dec 14, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Vol. 14 No. 23 Issue Date: Dec 28, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Vol. 15 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 25, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Vol. 15 No. 2 Issue Date: Feb 8, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Vol. 15 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 22, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Vol. 15 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 8, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Vol. 15 No. 5 Issue Date: Apr 1, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Vol. 15 No. 6 Issue Date: Apr 12, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Vol. 15 No. 7 Issue Date: Apr 26, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Vol. 15 No. 8 Issue Date: May 10, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 15 No. 9 Issue Date: May 24, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 15 No. 10 Issue Date: Jun 7, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 15 No. 11 Issue Date: Jun 21, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 15 No. 12 Issue Date: Jul 5, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 15 No. 13 Issue Date: Jul 26, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 15 No. 14 Issue Date: Aug 30, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 15 No. 15 Issue Date: Sep 13, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 15 No. 16 Issue Date: Sep 27, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 15 No. 17 Issue Date: Oct 11, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 15 No. 18 Issue Date: Oct 25, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 15 No. 19 Issue Date: Nov 8, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 15 No. 20 Issue Date: Nov 22, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 15 No. 21 Issue Date: Dec 6, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 15 No. 22 Issue Date: Dec 20, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 16 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 17, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 16 No. 2 Issue Date: Jan 31, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 16 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 14, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 16 No. 4 Issue Date: Feb 28, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 16 No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 14, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 16 No. 6 Issue Date: Mar 28, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Vol. 16 No. 7 Issue Date: Apr 11, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Vol. 16 No. 8 Issue Date: Apr 25, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Vol. 16 No. 9 Issue Date: May 9, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Vol. 16 No. 10 Issue Date: May 23, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Vol. 16 No. 11 Issue Date: Jun 6, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Vol. 16 No. 12 Issue Date: Jun 20, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Vol. 16 No. 13 Issue Date: Jul 11, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Vol. 16 No. 14 Issue Date: Aug 8, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Vol. 16 No. 15 Issue Date: Sep 12, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Vol. 16 No. 16 Issue Date: Sep 26, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Vol. 16 No. 17 Issue Date: Oct 10, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Vol. 16 No. 18 Issue Date: Oct 24, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Vol. 16 No. 19 Issue Date: Nov 7, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Vol. 16 No. 20 Issue Date: Nov 21, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Vol. 16 No. 21 Issue Date: Dec 5, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 16 No. 22 Issue Date: Dec 19, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 17 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 16, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 17 No. 2 Issue Date: Jan 30, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 17 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 13, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 17 No. 4 Issue Date: Feb 27, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 17 No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 12, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 17 No. 6 Issue Date: Mar 26, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 17 No. 7 Issue Date: Apr 9, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 17 No. 8 Issue Date: Apr 23, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 17 No. 9 Issue Date: May 7, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 17 No. 10 Issue Date: May 21, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 17 No. 11 Issue Date: Jun 4, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 17 No. 12 Issue Date: Jun 25, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 17 No. 13 Issue Date: Jul 9, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 17 No. 14 Issue Date: Jul 30, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 17 No. 15 Issue Date: Sep 10, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 17 No. 16 Issue Date: Sep 24, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 17 No. 17 Issue Date: Oct 8, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 17 No. 18 Issue Date: Oct 22, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 17 No. 19 Issue Date: Nov 5, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Vol. 17 No. 20 Issue Date: Nov 26, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Vol. 17 No. 21 Issue Date: Dec 10, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Vol. 17 No. 22 Issue Date: Dec 24, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Vol. 18 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 14, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Vol. 18 No. 2 Issue Date: Jan 28, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Vol. 18 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 11, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Vol. 18 No. 4 Issue Date: Feb 25, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Vol. 18 No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 11, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Vol. 18 No. 6 Issue Date: Mar 25, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Vol. 18 No. 7 Issue Date: Apr 8, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Vol. 18 No. 8 Issue Date: Apr 22, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Vol. 18 No. 9 Issue Date: May 6, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Vol. 18 No. 10 Issue Date: May 20, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Vol. 18 No. 11 Issue Date: Jun 3, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Vol. 18 No. 12 Issue Date: Jun 17, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Vol. 18 No. 13 Issue Date: Jul 15, 1977 (I) (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Vol. 18 No. 13 Issue Date: Jul 15, 1977 (II) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 18 No. 14 Issue Date: Aug 26, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 18 No. 15 Issue Date: Sep 16, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 18 No. 16 Issue Date: Sep 30, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 18 No. 17 Issue Date: Oct 21, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 18 No. 18 Issue Date: Nov 4, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 18 No. 19 Issue Date: Nov 25, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 18 No. 20 Issue Date: Dec 9, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 18 No. 21 Issue Date: Dec 23, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 19 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 13, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 19 No. 2 Issue Date: Jan 27, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 19 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 10, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 19 No. 4 Issue Date: Feb 24, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 19 No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 10, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 19 No. 6 Issue Date: Mar 24, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 19 No. 7 Issue Date: Apr 7, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 19 No. 8 Issue Date: Apr 21, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 19 No. 9 Issue Date: May 5, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 19 No. [no issue] May 19, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 19 No. 10 Issue Date: Jun 9, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 19 No. 11 Issue Date: Jun 30, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Vol. 19 No. 12 Issue Date: Jul 21, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Vol. 19 No. 13 Issue Date: Aug 25, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Vol. 19 No. 14 Issue Date: Sep 8, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Vol. 19 No. 15 Issue Date: Sep 22, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Vol. 19 No. 16 Issue Date: Oct 6, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Vol. 19 No. 17 Issue Date: Oct 20, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Vol. 19 No. 18 Issue Date: Nov 3, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Vol. 19 No. 19 Issue Date: Nov 17, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Vol. 19 No. 20 Issue Date: Dec 1, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Vol. 19 No. 21 Issue Date: Dec 15, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Vol. 19 No. 22 Issue Date: Dec 29, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 20 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 26, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 20 No. 2 Issue Date: Feb 9, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 20 No. 3 Issue Date: Feb 23, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Vol. 20 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 9, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 20 No. 5 Issue Date: Mar 23, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Vol. 20 No. 6 Issue Date: Apr 6, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 20 No. 7 Issue Date: Apr 20, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 20 No. 8 Issue Date: May 4, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Vol. 20 No. 9 Issue Date: May 18, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 20 No. 10 Issue Date: Jun 1, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 20 No. 11 Issue Date: Jun 15, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 20 No. 12 Issue Date: Jun 29, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 20 No. 13 Issue Date: Jul 13, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 20 No. 14 Issue Date: Aug 31, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 20 No. 15 Issue Date: Sep 14, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 20 No. 16 Issue Date: Sep 28, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 20 No. 17 Issue Date: Oct 12, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 20 No. 18 Issue Date: Oct 26, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 20 No. 19 Issue Date: Nov 16, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 20 No. 20 Issue Date: Dec 7, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Vol. 20 No. 21 Issue Date: Dec 21, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Vol. 21 No. 1 Issue Date: Jan 18, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Vol. 21 No. 2 Issue Date: Feb 1, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 24)